Guide to the Stanford University, Provost's Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Budget Files, 1973-1981; Accession ARCH-1985-080
  - University Counsel, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - University Libraries, equipment needs, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Values, Technology and Society Program, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Values, Technology and Society Program, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Computer costs realocation, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - SCIP background material on administrative computing, Undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - SCIP background material on administrative computing, Undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - SCIP background material on administrative computing, Undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - SCIP background material on administrative computing, Undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - DOSA, budget protocol letter, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Accreditation Records, 2000-2010; Accession ARCH-2011-339 (Box 1)
- WASC accreditation reports, 2008-2012; Accession ARCH-2013-033
  - Institutional Proposal for Reaccreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 39583 (Box 1)
  - Appendices for the Institutional Proposal for Reaccreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 39583 (Box 1)
  - Capacity and Preparatory Review Report for the Reaffirmation of Accreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 2010 Dec (Box 1)
  - Appendices for the Capacity and Preparatory Review Report for the Reaffirmation of Accreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 2010 Dec (Box 1)
  - Educational Effectiveness Review Report for the Reaffirmation of Accreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 2012 Oct (Box 1)
  - Appendices 1-19 for Educational Effectiveness Review Report for the Reaffirmation of Accreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 2012 Oct (Box 1)
  - Appendices 20-30 for Educational Effectiveness Review Report for the Reaffirmation of Accreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 2012 Oct (Box 1)